<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>business on Sushanth Kurdekar</title><link>https://www.logicalbee.in/tags/business/</link><description>Recent content in business on Sushanth Kurdekar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>sushanth@logicalbee.in (Sushanth Kurdekar)</managingEditor><webMaster>sushanth@logicalbee.in (Sushanth Kurdekar)</webMaster><copyright>2022 logicalbee All rights reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.logicalbee.in/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5 Steps To Making Money With You Affiliate Marketing</title><link>https://www.logicalbee.in/5-steps-to-making-money-with-you-affiliate-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>sushanth@logicalbee.in (Sushanth Kurdekar)</author><guid>https://www.logicalbee.in/5-steps-to-making-money-with-you-affiliate-marketing/</guid><description>Hey! hey you..!
If you are working 9-5 job wich you dont like, then you are in the right place. there is much more we can achive in our life than that. making money online is an art, In this pandamic situation there is no garantee that your job may not be served longer, be your own boss, and live a life with freedom.
What is Affiliate Marketing? Choose a high profitable niche Choose Best product to promote Choose a traffic source/platform Add value &amp;amp; build your brand Build an automated sales funnel {:toc} What is Affiliate Marketing?</description></item><item><title>How to Make Money Online in India</title><link>https://www.logicalbee.in/how-to-make-money-online-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>sushanth@logicalbee.in (Sushanth Kurdekar)</author><guid>https://www.logicalbee.in/how-to-make-money-online-in-india/</guid><description>Table of Contents Make Money with Blogging Making Maney with YouTube Making Maney with Affiliate Marketing How to receive payments? {:toc} How to make money online in India? In thease days people perticulerly in india searching such kind of queries on internet. There are few such resourses there thay will provide provision to earn money online through their website. Here i will try to give some tips that where you can exectly make some real money in dollers.</description></item><item><title>How To Start A Blog - 2020</title><link>https://www.logicalbee.in/how-to-start-a-blog-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>sushanth@logicalbee.in (Sushanth Kurdekar)</author><guid>https://www.logicalbee.in/how-to-start-a-blog-2020/</guid><description>Hey,
What’s up? It’s Sushanth here…
First, I would like to personally thank you for click on this article. I hope I​t will definitely help you! I will keep this article in a short and simple, step-by-step guide on how to start a blog? One special thing is you don&amp;rsquo;t need any previous experience to create a blog by your own this guide is for beginners in blogging.
In this article, I’m not going to write theory kind of stuff, like what is blogging Bla bla bla.</description></item></channel></rss>